Guide to the Herbert Brodkin Television Production Files
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Herbert Brodkin Television Production Files
1953-1972
YCAL MSS 281
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
30
(30 boxes)
The Herbert Brodkin Television Production Files document the work of producer Herbert Brodkin from 1953 to 1972, and television content generally during what is often called its "golden age." The collection consists of Brodkin's bound copies of scripts and related production files for some of the programs that he produced, including the The Defenders, The Nurses, Brenner, Coronet Blue, and numerous episodes for anthologies such as The Alcoa Hour and The Elgin Hour. Contents of the production files vary for each episode, and can include shooting schedules; production reports; staff, crew and cast lists; budgets; photographs and contact sheets of production stills; reviews; blueprints; and rights and permissions.
Brodkin, Herbert, 1912-1990
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Herbert Brodkin, 1972.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Herbert Brodkin (1912-1990)
Herbert Brodkin was a successful and influential television producer whose work spanned the first four decades of the medium. Concentrating chiefly on dramatic programming, he worked for sponsored anthologies including The Alcoa Hour and The Motorola TV Hour in the 1950s, and then went on to produce popular series such as the courtroom drama The Defenders and the hospital drama The Nurses in the 1960s. Brodkin's programs, and those produced by his companies Plautus Productions and Titus Productions, frequently explored controversial social, ethical, and political issues including addiction, abortion, euthanasia, racism, blacklisting, and war crimes.
Brodkin was born on November 9, 1912, in New York City, to Russian immigrant parents. He earned a B.A. in drama from the University of Michigan and an M.F.A. in directing and set design from the Yale School of Drama. Before his career in television began in the late 1940s, he worked in the theatre in and around New York City, and as a filmmaker for the U.S. Army Signal Corps during World War II. He died on October 29, 1990, in New York.
Scope and Contents
The Herbert Brodkin Television Production Files document the work of producer Herbert Brodkin from 1953 to 1972, and television content generally during what is often called its "golden age." The collection consists of Brodkin's bound copies of scripts and related production files for some of the programs that he produced, including the The Defenders, The Nurses, Brenner, Coronet Blue, and numerous episodes for anthologies such as The Alcoa Hour and The Elgin Hour. Contents of the production files vary for each episode, and can include shooting schedules; production reports; staff, crew and cast lists; budgets; photographs and contact sheets of production stills; reviews; blueprints; and rights and permissions.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by program title. Under the heading for each title, bound scripts are arranged by volume number. Following each volume are production files that correspond with the episodes in that volume.
Television programs -- United States; Television scripts; Television -- Production and direction -- United States -- Archives; Brodkin, Herbert, 1912-1990
- The Alcoa Hour - Goodyear Playhouse, 1955-56
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Production files, 1955, undated (Box 1, Folder 2-5)
    Scope and Contents
    The Expendable House
    The Black Wings
    A Business Proposition
    The Small Servant
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Production files, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7-10)
    The Mechanical Heart
    A Girl Can Tell
    One Mummy Too Many
    Thunder In Washington
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Production files, 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 12-15)
    The Trees
    Undertow
    Christmas Til Closing
    Rise Up And Walk
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Production files, 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 17-20)
    Man On A Tiger
    The Land Is Mine
    A Patch On Faith
    The Starlet
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Production files, 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 22-25)
    Long After Summer
    Kyria Katina
    Tragedy In A Temporary Town
    The Terrorists
  - Scripts (Volume 6), 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Production files, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27-30)
    Man On Fire
    Conspiracy Of Hearts
    Dollface
    Joey
  - Scripts (Volume 7), 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Production files, 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 32-35)
    Finkle's Comet
    Footlight Frenzy
    Even The Weariest River
    Career Girl
  - Scripts (Volume 8), 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Production files, 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 37-40)
    Paris and Mrs. Pearlman
    The Sentry
    President
    In The Days Of Our Youth
  - Scripts (Volume 9), 1955-56 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Production files, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 42-44)
    The Confidence Man
    The Primary Colors
    The Magic Horn
- Brenner, 1958-59
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Production files, 1958-59 (Box 3, Folder 46-49)
    The Thin Line
    Blind Spot
    Loan Shark
    Record Of Arrest
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Production files, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 51-54)
    Point Of Law
    Family Man
    Thin Ice
    Word Of Honor
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Production files, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 56-59)
    Small Take
    Man In The Middle
    Crime Wave
    False Witness
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Production files, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 61-64)
    The Buff
    I, Executioner
    The Long Reach
    The Law Is Suspect
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Production files, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 66-70)
    Monopoly On Fear
    Good Friend
    Departmental Trial
    Crises
    Unwritten Law
  - Scripts (Volume 6), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Production files, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 72-76)
    Finger Man
    Laney's Boy
    The Plain Truth
    The Vigilantes
    Charlie Paradise
- CBS Playhouse - Dear Friends, 1967
  - Scripts, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Production Files, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 78-80)
- CBS Playhouse - People Next Door, 1968-70
  - Scripts, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Production Files, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 82-86)
  - Scripts, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Production Files, 1969-70 (Box 4, Folder 88-94)
- CBS Studio One, 1957-58
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1957 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Production files, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 96-98)
    The Hollywood Complex
    The Defender (Parts 1-2)
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1957 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Production files, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 100-102)
    A Child Is Waiting
    Walk Down The Hill
    A Member Of The Family
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1957 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Production files, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 104-107)
    The Years In Between
    The Playwright And Star
    The Rice Sprout Song
    The Traveling Lady
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Production files, 1957-58 (Box 5, Folder 109-112)
    The Deaf Heart
    The Bend In The Road
    24 Hours 'til Dawn
    Please Report Any Odd Characters
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Production files and Final Cost Sheets, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 114-117)
    Escape Route
    No Deadly Medicine (Part 1 & 2)
- Center Stage, 1954
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Production files, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 119-123)
    Chivalry At Howling Creek
    Grandfather Takes Off
    The Human Touch
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Production files, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 125-127)
    Golden Anniversary
    Luckie Louie
    The Desdemona Murder Case
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Production files, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 129-131)
    The Worthy Opponent
    The Day Before Atlanta
    The Heart Of A Clown
- Coronet Blue, 1965-66
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Production files, 1965-66 (Box 6, Folder 133-138)
    A Time To Be Born
    Where You From And What You Done
    A Dozen Demons
    Faces
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 140-142)
    Six Months To Mars
    The Assassins
    Tomoyo
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 144-146)
    Man Running
    A Charade For Murder
    The Flip Side Of Jimmy Devon
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 148-150)
    The Rebels
    Saturday
    The Presence Of Evil
- The Defenders, 1960-65
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1960-61 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Production files, 1960-61 (Box 6, Folder 152-155)
    Death Across The Counter
    The Accident
    The Crusader
    The Riot
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Production files, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 157-160)
    The Man With The Concrete Thumb
    The Trial Of Jenny Scott
    The Boy Who Had No Luck
    The Hundred Lives Of Harry Simms
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Production files, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 162-165)
    The Best Defense
    Bedside Murder
    Perjury
    Killer Instinct
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Production files, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 167-170)
    Young Lovers
    Quality Of Mercy
    The Treadmill
    The Empty Chute
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Production files, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 172-175)
    Storm At Birch Glen
    The Prowler
    The Benefactor
    The Search
  - Scripts (Volume 6), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Production files, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 177-180)
    The Iron Man
    The Point Shaver
    The Attack
    The Locked Room
  - Scripts (Volume 7), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Production files, 1961-62 (Box 8, Folder 182-185)
    Gideon's Follies
    The Hickory Indian
    The Tarnished Cross
    The Last Six Months
  - Scripts (Volume 8), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 187-190)
    The Naked Heiress
    Reunion With Death
    Along Came A Spider
    The Broken Barrelhead
  - Scripts (Volume 9), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 192-195)
    Blood County
    The Seven Ghosts Of Simon Gray
    The Voices Of Death
    The Indelible Silence
  - Scripts (Volume 10), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 197-200)
    The Avenger
    Grandma TNT
    The Unwanted
    The Hidden Jungle
  - Scripts (Volume 11), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 202-205)
    The Madman I
    The Madman II
    Death Takes The Stand
    The Bigamist
  - Scripts (Volume 12), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 207-210)
    The Invisible Badge
    The Apostle
    Kill Or Be Killed
    A Man Against Himself
  - Scripts (Volume 13), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 212-215)
    The Savage Infant
    The Poisoned Fruit Doctrine
    Poltergeist
    Ordeal
  - Scripts (Volume 14), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 217-220)
    The Traitor
    The Eye Of Fear
    Metamorphosis
    The Hour Before Doomsday
  - Scripts (Volume 15), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Production files, 1962-63 (Box 9, Folder 222-225)
    The Last Illusion
    The Heathen
    The Taste Of Vengeance
    A Book For Burning
  - Scripts (Volume 16), 1963 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 227-230)
    The Colossus
    Judgment Eve
    The Brother Killers
    The Noose
  - Scripts (Volume 17), 1963 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 232-235)
    Everybody Else Is Dead
    The Trial Of Twenty-Two
    Loophole
    Conspiracy Of Silence
  - Scripts (Volume 18), 1963 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 237-240)
    The Cruel Hook
    The Crowd Pleaser
    The Empty Heart
    Claire Cheval Died In Boston
  - Scripts (Volume 19), 1963 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 242-245)
    The Weeping Baboon
    The Captive
    The Bagman
    The Star-Spangled Ghetto
  - Scripts (Volume 20), 1963 (Box 10, Folder 246)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 247-250)
    Fugue For Trumpet And Small Boy
    The Seal Of Confession
    Who'll Dig His Grave?
    The Gentle Assassin
  - Scripts (Volume 21), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 252-255)
    The Man Who Served His Country
    Old Lady Ironsides
    Death Watch
    Blacklist
  - Scripts (Volume 22), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 256)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 257-260)
    All The Silent Voices
    The Secret
    A Taste Of Ashes
    The Pill Man
  - Scripts (Volume 23), 1963-64 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Production files, 1963-64 (Box 11, Folder 262-265)
    Die Laughing
    Drink Like A Lady
    Survival
    Moment Of Truth
  - Scripts (Volume 24), 1964 (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 267-270)
    The Hidden Fury
    Fade Away
    The Thief
    Yankee Come Home
  - Scripts (Volume 25), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 272-275)
    Mind Over Murder
    The Sixth Alarm
    The Fine Line
    The Non-Violent
  - Scripts (Volume 26), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 276)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 277-279)
    Stowaway
    Hollow Triumph
    The Uncivil War
  - Scripts (Volume 27), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 281-283)
    The 700 Year Old Gang
    Hero Of The People
    Comeback
  - Scripts (Volume 28), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 284)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 285-288)
    Conflict Of Interests
    Turning Point
    King Of The Hill
    Go-Between
  - Scripts (Volume 29), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 289)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 290-293)
    The Siege
    The Man Who
    Whitewash
    A Voice Loud And Clear
  - Scripts (Volume 30), 1964 (Box 13, Folder 294)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 295-298)
    Eyewitness
    Whipping Boy
    Silent Killer
    Death On Wheels
  - Scripts (Volume 31), 1964 (Box 13, Folder 299)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 300-303)
    The Unwritten Law
    The Objector
    Fires Of The Mind
    No-Knock
  - Scripts (Volume 32), 1964-65 (Box 13, Folder 304)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 305-308)
    The Merry-Go-Round Mender
    Nobody Asks What Side You're On
    Impeachment
    The Sworn Twelve
  - Scripts (Volume 33), 1965 (Box 13, Folder 309)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 310-316)
    A Matter Of Law And Disorder
    Youths And Maidens On An Evening Walk
    The Prosecutor
    The Bums' Rush
    Only A Child
- The Elgin Hour, 1954-55
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 317)
  - Production files, 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 318-322)
    Flood
    Family Crisis
    High Man
    Warm Clay
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 323)
  - Production files, 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 324-327)
    Hearts And Hollywood
    Yesterday's Magic
    Falling Star
    The Bridge
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 328)
  - Production files, 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 329-332)
    Family Meeting
    Days Of Grace
    Sting Of Death
    Crime In The Streets
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 333)
  - Production files, 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 334-337)
    The $1,000 Window
    Black Eagle Pass
    Midsummer Melody
    Driftwood
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 338)
  - Production files, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 339-341)
    San Francisco Fracas
    Mind Over Momma
    Combat Medics
- Espionage, 1962-64
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1962-63 (Box 15, Folder 342)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 343-346)
    The Incurable One
    The Whistling Shrimp
    The Weakling
    He Rises On Sunday And We On Monday
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 347)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 348-351)
    A Covenant With Death
    The Gentle Spies
    The Dragon Slayer
    To The Very End
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 352)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 353-356)
    A Camel To Ride, A Sheep To Eat
    The Light Of A Friendly Star
    A Tiny Drop Of Poison
    Festival Of Pawns
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 357)
  - Production files, 1963-64 (Box 15, Folder 358-361)
    Never Turn Your Back On A Friend
    Medal For A Turned Coat
    The Final Decision
    Do You Remember Leo Winters?
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 362)
  - Production files, 1963-64 (Box 15, Folder 363-366)
    We The Hunted
    The Frantick Rebel
    Castles In Spain
    Snow On Mount Kama
  - Scripts (Volume 6), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 367)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 368-371)
    Once A Spy
    The Liberators
    A Free Agent
    Some Other Kind Of World
- For The People, 1964-65
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 372)
  - Production files, 1964-65 (Box 16, Folder 373-376)
    The Killing Of One Human Being
    Guilt Shall Not Escape Nor Innocence Suffer
    The Influence Of Fear
    To Prosecute All Crimes
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1965 (Box 16, Folder 377)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 378-381)
    Between Candor And Shame
    Act Of Violence
    Secure Any Special Privilege Or Advantage
    Dangerous To The Public Peace And Safety
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1965 (Box 16, Folder 382)
  - Production files, 1964-65 (Box 16, Folder 383-388)
    The Right To Kill
    With Intent To Influence
    Seized, Confined, and Detained
    Any Benevolent Purpose
    A Competent Witness
- Lights Out (When Widows Weep), Crawlspace, Rx For The Defense (The Prisoner of Plattsville), 1971-72, undated
  - Scripts, 1971-72 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - Production Files, 1971-72, undated (Box 17, Folder 390-401)
- The Motorola TV Hour, 1953-54
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1953-54 (Box 17, Folder 402)
  - Production files, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 403-407)
    Outlaw's Reckoning
    Westward The Sun
    Brandenburg Gate
    At Ease
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1953-54 (Box 17, Folder 408)
  - Production files, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 409-412)
    The Thirteen Clocks
    The Last Days Of Hitler
    Side By Side
    A Dash Of Bitters
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1953-54 (Box 17, Folder 413)
  - Production files, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 414-417)
    The Muldoon Matter
    The Family Man
    Nightmare In Algiers
    The Sins Of The Fathers
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1953-54 (Box 17, Folder 418)
  - Production files, 1953-54 (Box 17, Folder 419-421)
    Black Chiffon
    Love Song
    Atomic Attack
- The Nurses, 1962-65
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1962 (Box 17, Folder 422)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 423-426)
    Night Shift
    The Barbara Bowers Story
    Frieda
    Fly, Shadow
  - Scripts (Volume 2), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 427)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 428-431)
    A Strange And Distant Place
    A Private Room
    The Walls Came Tumbling Down
    Dr. Lillian
  - Scripts (Volume 3), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 432)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 433-436)
    The Prisoner
    The Thunder Of Ernie Bass
    Image Of Angela
    Two Black Candles
  - Scripts (Volume 4), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 437)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 438-441)
    Root Of Violence
    The Soft Touch
    Lady Made Of Stone
    The Third Generation
  - Scripts (Volume 5), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 442)
  - Production files, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 443-446)
    Many A Sullivan
    The Perfect Nurse
    Circle Of Choice
    A Difference Of Years
  - Scripts (Volume 6), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 447)
  - Production files, 1962-63 (Box 18, Folder 448-451)
    Night Sounds
    You Could Die Laughing
    The Life
    The Saturday Evening Of Time
  - Scripts (Volume 7), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 452)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 453-456)
    Call Girl
    A Question Of Time
    A Dark World
    Express Stop From Lenox Avenue
  - Scripts (Volume 8), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 457)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 458-461)
    Choice Among Wrongs
    They Are As Lions
    Bitter Pill
    Field Of Battle
  - Scripts (Volume 9), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 462)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 463-466)
    No Score
    Show Just Cause Why You Should Weep
    The Gift
  - Scripts (Volume 10), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 467)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 468-471)
    Strike
    The Witch Of The East Wing
    The Horn Of Plenty
    Apple Strudel
  - Scripts (Volume 11), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 472)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 473-476)
    Rally Round My Comrades
    Disaster Call
  - Scripts (Volume 12), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 477)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 478-481)
    Credo
    The Helping Hand
    To Spend, To Give, To Want
    The Seeing Heart
  - Scripts (Volume 13), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 482)
  - Production files, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 483-486)
    The Interne Syndrome
    Rainbow Ride
    Edward Victor de Marino
    The Imperfect Prodigy
  - Scripts (Volume 14), 1963-64 (Box 20, Folder 487)
  - Production files, 1963-64 (Box 20, Folder 488-491)
    The Roamer
    Nurse Is A Feminine Noun
    For The Mice And The Rabbits
    The Forever Child
  - Scripts (Volume 15), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 492)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 493-496)
    Climb A Broken Ladder
    A Kind Of Loving
    The Leopard Killer
    The Gismo On The EEG
  - Scripts (Volume 16), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 497)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 498-501)
    The Human Transaction
    To All My Friends On Shore
    A Postcard From Yucatan
    White On White
  - Scripts (Volume 17), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 502)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 503-506)
    The Bystanders
    Where Park Runs Into Vreeland
    The Warrior
    The Love Of A Smart Operator
  - Scripts (Volume 18), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 507)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 508-511)
    Hildie
    Time For You And Time For Me
    The Respect For One Another
    Once Bitten
  - Scripts (Volume 19), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 512)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 513-515)
    No Shadow Where There Is No Sun
    The Outpost
    A Family Resemblance
  - Scripts (Volume 20), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 516)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 517-519)
    The Suspect (Parts 1-2)
    The Skill In These Hands
    So Some Girls Play The Cello
  - Scripts (Volume 21), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 520)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 521-524)
    Next Stop, Valhalla
    Rites Of Spring
    A Messenger To Everyone
    Last Rites For A Rag Doll
  - Scripts (Volume 22), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 525)
  - Production files, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 526-529)
    The Patient Nurse
    A Couple Dozen Of Tiny Pills
    Night Of The Watch
    A Question Of Murder
  - Scripts (Volume 23), 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 530)
  - Production files, 1964-65 (Box 22, Folder 531-534)
    Sixteen Hours To Chicago
    A Dangerous Silence
    Where There's Smoke
  - Scripts (Volume 24), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 535)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 536-539)
    The Politicians
    April Thaw Of Dr. Mai
    Threshold
    A39846
  - Scripts (Volume 25), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 540)
  - Production files, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 541-543)
    The Witnesses
    The Heroine
    An Unweeded Garden
- The Nurses - ABC, 1965-67
  - Scripts (Volume 1-6), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 544-549)
  - Scripts (Volume 7-19), 1965-66 (Box 23, Folder 550-562)
  - Scripts (Volume 20-31), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 563-574)
  - Scripts (Volume 32-43), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 575-586)
  - Scripts (Volume 44-55), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 587-598)
  - Scripts (Volume 56-67), 1966-67 (Box 27, Folder 599-610)
  - Scripts (Volume 68-79), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 611-622)
- Playhouse 90, 1958-60
  - Scripts (Volume 1), 1958 (Box 29, Folder 623)